20six.co.uk 2005-03-08

# 20six — Get your own Weblog. Blogging by SMS, MMS or E-Mail, too.

Legal

| 

## Our privacy promise

Your privacy is important to us. We hold that you are the owner of information about yourself and we promise that: 

  * We will only use your information to improve the quality and relevance of the communications we send you and your experience here. 
  * You may update or change your information held by us at any time. 

Once you have registered, choose Public Info from the left-hand list to update your details. 
  * **General issues**  
Why we ask for information 
    * Our business is based on a simple deal. We will provide you with a service that let’s you create your own weblog, or online diary, and interact with other people using our service. 
    * In order to do this, we work on your behalf to create marketing messages, offers and promotions which are relevant, useful and unique. In return we ask that you give us information about yourself which we can use in planning our offers. 
The information we ask for 
    * On joining, you are asked for a small amount of information. We ask for enough contact information to ensure that we can reach you when we need to. From time to time, we'll ask you for more information about yourself to help us improve the service. 
    * Additionally, you can optionally provide information about your interests, such as your favourite films and books. You can make this information available to other users so that they can find your blog or make contact with you from time to time. 
    * This information will be stored with the other information we hold about you and you may change, update or remove it at any time. 
What information we don't ask for 
    * We don’t ask you for any payment information, although if you choose to take a paid-for service from 20six, we will need this information. 
What we do with the information we gather 
    * We use the information we get from you to make sure that whenever we send you a marketing message, a special offer or a promotion, it is relevant and as useful as possible. 
    * We may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with legal processes, we do not sell or otherwise share personally identifiable information with third parties without your consent except in the following instances: 
      * unless required by applicable law or pursuant to a court or similar order; 
      * as deemed necessary, in our discretion, to protect the legal rights or the property of the Company, a registered user or third party, or to prevent personal injury; and/or 
      * where we are approached with regard to the potential sale of the Company's business and/or assets or with regard to any joint venture arrangement, in such circumstances we reserve the right to pass on such personally identifiable information to our advisors and any prospective purchaser, as well as to any relevant parties.

  * **Contacting us**  

    * You may contact us at any time to discuss the information we hold about you, to request that we change it or to remove it. Or e-mail ukprivacy@20six.net 

  * **Specific issues**  

    * Cookies   
When you log in to the service a cookie is set on your computer. This cookie is used for session tracking purposes, helping us to keep a track of you as you move around the site. They allow us to analyse the popularity of the site and to better manage and improve the service we provide you. 
    * Your username   
When you join up, you are asked to choose a username. This is the unique name you use every time you log in and no other member may have the same username. 
    * IP number logging   
The service logs IP numbers for statistical reasons. We do not tie IP numbers to sessions and do not use IP numbers for identification purposes. 
    * Protection of your information   
The service uses an advanced security system that protects your information from unauthorised use. Member information is held on computers not directly connected to the Internet and inaccessible from the outside. 
    * Changing, correcting or updating the information we hold   
We'd like you to keep the information we keep about you up-to-date and you may change any of the basic information we keep about you (except your name, date of birth and gender) at any time by visiting your info. Click on the your info link after you have logged in to see or edit the information we hold on you. 

  * **Partner sites**  
We think that our way of doing things is important and our Privacy Promise should always apply to users. However, sometimes-when we provide the service \- to users of other web sites, for instance - it may not be possible to apply the Promise in its entirety. Usually the partner web site will have its own privacy policy and we will check this policy before we agree to work together to make sure it meets our standards.   
If you are a user of one of these partner web sites and you want to discuss your privacy, you may need to talk to the web site owner directly. While you are using the service, it will always be clear which site's privacy policy and terms & conditions apply and to whom you need to speak for help. 

---|---
